(Psychic:)All right, why don't we begin?
(Psychic:)Your spirit guides are telling me
that there's a woman in your life
(Psychic:)-you're having problems with.
-That's an easy guess.
(Sheldon:)I'm clearly an annoying person
and have problems with both genders.
(Psychic:)Yes, you clearly are.
(Psychic:)But I'm seeing a specific woman
(Psychic:)that you're in a romantic
relationship with.
(Penny:)Oh, oh, here we go.
(Psychic:)-Does she have dark hair?
-Yes! Yes!
Your spirit guides are on fire!
(Sheldon:)The majority of people
have dark hair.
(Sheldon:)Even you, at one time.
(Psychic:)Does she work
in a similar field to you?
Ha! The opposite.
She's a neurobiclogist,
and I'm a theoretical physicist.
(Sheldon:)My spirit guides can go suck an egg.
(Psychic:)They're telling me that you have
difficulty being close with her.